export const Questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Alabama?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Indianapolis",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceA",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Alaska?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Juneau",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceB",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Pennsylvania?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Harrisburg",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceB",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Massachusetts?",
    choiceA: "Boston",
    choiceB: "Indianapolis",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceA",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Nevada?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Juneau",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Carson City",
    answer: "choiceD",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state New_York?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Phoenix",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Albany",
    answer: "choiceD",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Rhode_Island?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Providence",
    choiceC: "Harrisburg",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceB",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Texas?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Austin",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceB",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Wyoming?",
    choiceA: "Cheyenne",
    choiceB: "Phoenix",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceA",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    prompt: "What is the capitol of the state Montana?",
    choiceA: "Montgomery",
    choiceB: "Helena",
    choiceC: "Annapolis",
    choiceD: "Jackson",
    answer: "choiceB",
  },
  
];
